

xpeke.og@gmail.com



315-i P. Dela Cruz St. San Bartolome, Quezon City Philippines 1116

SKILLS:

- Creativity
- Leadership
- Organized
- Problem-solving
- Teamwork
- Time management
- Detail-oriented
- Flexible under any situation
- High-level of maintaning focus on any tasks given

COMMON TOOLS USED:























JOSHUA RAMOS

Front-End Developer & Designer

ABOUT ME

Talented, unique and passionate Front-End Developer with multiple extensive experiences in creating persuasive and attractive marketing and communication materials. Throughout my work experiences, I have accumulated various technical skills in use of WEB DESIGN / DEVELOPMENT ADOBE CREATIVE CLOUD and UI/UX Protoyping.

Expert at developing effective campaigns and advertisements to increase visibility, branding, business growth and development through Search Engine Optimization (SEO)

EDUCATION

San Francisco Elementary School

2003 - 2009 Diploma

Sergio Osmena Sr. High School

2009 - 2013 Diploma

FreeCodeCamp

2014 - 2015 Certification in Responsive Web Design 2022 - 2022

Certification in JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures

EXPERIENCE

Tectonic Works LTD. - U.K Based

Front-End Developer in UI/UX (May 2017 - Aug 2018)

Illustrating design ideas using storyboards, process flows and sitemaps.

Designing graphic user interface elements like menus, tabs and widgets.

One Multimedia Access - PH Based

Multimedia Artist (Nov 2019 - Dec 2020)

Developing briefing, brochures, multimedia presentations, web pages promotional products and technical illustrations

SiteBru - U.K Based

Web Developer (Sep 2022 - May 2023)

Proficiency in HTML, CSS, JavaScript and other web development technologies such as CMS has enabled me to create responsive and interactive websites that provide and engaging user experience